[Waco] Daughters of the American Revolution: Henry Downs Chapter records, Inclusive: 1897-2006, undated, Bulk: 1960-1990
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Literary Productions, 1900-2001; 5
  - Essay: Carol Jo Smith: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Elise Wilson: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Essay: Jason Evans: Concerning Francis Marion, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Amy Kiphen: Concerning Francis Marion, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Essay: Jeff Holder: Concerning Francis Marion, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Essay: Francisco Saliras: Concerning Francis Marion, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Jay Ducharme: Concerning John Marshall, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Damon Turner: Concerning Hirem Maxim, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Marcus Hensel: Concerning Cyrus McCormick, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Jessica Reyna: Concerning Cyrus McCormick, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Michael Crain: Concerning Jane McKisick, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Julie Burns: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Maria Moreno: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Essay: Ryan Mueller: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Tina Neely: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Essay: Kirsten Schulte: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Essay: Jana Ziegler: Concerning Samuel Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Essay: Carrie Kramoles: Concerning Elisha Otis, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Essay: Jynetta Hamilton: Concerning James Otis, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Essay: Wendy Johnson: Concerning Thomas Paine, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Essay: Jason Littleton: Concerning Thomas Paine, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Essay: Emmalee Peacock: Concerning Thomas Paine, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Essay: Laquita Williams: Concerning Thomas Paine, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Essay: Jason Shilling: Concerning Painting, undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Essay: Joelle Wall: Concerning Cynthia Parker, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Essay: Garla Neal: Concerning Molly Pitcher, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Essay: Zhemyka Rosser: Concerning Molly Pitcher, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Essay: Jennifer Alexander: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Essay: Stephanie Beard: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Essay: Melissa Cates: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Essay: Joseph Chavez: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Essay: Kristen Fielder: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Essay: Ireshekia Hart: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Essay: Kristi Ingram: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Essay: Anita Kelly: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Essay: Joan Le: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Essay: Charlie Love: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Essay: Kerry Maus: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Essay: Chip Mayfield: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Essay: Angie McNeil: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Essay: Rickie Mirich: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Essay: Ryan Mueller: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Essay: Aimee Myers: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Essay: Crystal Rowe: Concerning Paul Revere, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Essay: Hayley Voige: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Aneece York: Concerning Paul Revere, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Ashley Kanger: Concerning Betsy Ross, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Essay: Misty Royals: Concerning Betsy Ross, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Essay: Jerri Simpson: Concerning Betsy Ross, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Essay: Lacy Sanders: Concerning Deborah Sampson, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Allison Storrs: Concerning Deborah Sampson, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Julie Robken: Concerning Roger Sherman, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Christy Dietz: Concerning Travel, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Ruthie Alexander: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Tiffany Bates: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Essay: Brent Coaney: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Essay: David Davis: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Seblewengel Elias: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Emily Erwin: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Essay: Joy Gage: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Angela Goff: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Essay: Adriana Gomez: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Nagda Guerrero: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Essay: Brent Holmes: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Essay: Michelle Holt: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Laura Humphrey: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Tarey Pack: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Linda Perez: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Theresa Powell: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Janice Sherrard: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Desharie Stevenson: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Steven Thomas: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Essay: Renee Vrana: Concerning George Washington, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Mary Vaughn: Concerning George Washington, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Essay: Robin Cockrell: Concerning James Watt, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Essay: David Hernandez: Concerning Anthony Wayne, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Essay: Shannon Brink: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Essay: John Hunt: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Essay: Cynthia Hutchison: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Essay: Emily Murphy: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Essay: Blake Petty: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Essay: Pavla Whitney: Concerning Eli Whitney, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Essay: Justin Dyke: Concerning Linus Yale, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Artifacts, 1957-1990; 6
  The following series is comprised of artifacts such as ribbons, plaques, and pins collected by the Henry Downs Chapter. The materials are in good condition.
  - Ribbons: Congress and Art Contests, 1984-1989 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Honor Roll: Henry Downs Chapter, 1957 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Pins: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1986, 1990, undated (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Certificate: Service Award, 1976 November 4 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Plaque: VAMC Farm Festival, 1984 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Medals, undated (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 7)
- Photographic Materials, undated; 7
  The following series contains photographic materials pertaining to past regents of the Henry Downs Chapter. The materials are in good condition.
  - Negatives: Regents, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Regents, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies: Regents, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Scrapbooks, 1901-2006, undated; 8
  This series is comprised of twenty-four scrapbooks organized by the Henry Downs Chapter. The scrapbooks were numbered according to the book’s date range. Based on the condition of the materials, some scrapbooks have been preserved while others were digitized. The latter can be found on Bearspace with the assistance of a staff member. Scrapbooks that were kept intact will be located in the oversized boxes of this series.
  - Scrapbook One: Loose Materials: Yearbook: 80th Anniversary, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 1-11, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 12-13, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 15-21, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 23-25, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 25-27, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 29-34, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 35-38, 1902-1962 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 40-46, 1902-1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 51, 1902-1962 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 52-53, 1902-1962 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 54-58, 1902-1962 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Two: Pages 58, 1902-1962 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 1, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 2-9, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 9-10, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 10-24, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 30-37, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 37-52, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 53-65, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 77-87, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 88-93, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 93-98, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 99-101, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 101, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Three: Pages 101-102, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 102, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 103, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 104, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 105, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 106, 1910-1956 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 107, 1910-1956 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 108, 1910-1956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 109, 1910-1956 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 110, 1910-1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Three: Page 111, 1910-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 1-2, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 8-31, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 32-35, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 37-45, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Four: Page 46, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 58-61, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 61-63, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Four: Pages 63-66, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Four: Page 68, 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 2-6, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 6-8, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 8-12, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 14-20, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Five: Page 21, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 21-30, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 31-32, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Five: Page 35, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 36-46, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 46-48, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 48-52, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 52-65, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 65-71, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 71-73, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 73-78, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Five: Page 83, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 83-93, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Five: Pages 94-95, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Five: Page 96, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 3-8, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 9-16, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 17-18, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 19-21, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 21-25, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Six: Page 27, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 29-38, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 39-45, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 46-51, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 51-52, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 53-55, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 55-60, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 61-62, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 63-68, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 68-69, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 70-74, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook Six: Page 74, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook Six: Pages 75-80, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 1-4, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 5-8, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 9-10, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 11-12, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 13-16, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Pages 17-23, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Seven: Page 25, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 1-10, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 11-15, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 16-21, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Page 22, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 24-25, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 26-37, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 37-44, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Page 45, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 46-47, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 48-58, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 62-65, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 66-72, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Page 75, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Nine: Pages 80-90, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 1-7, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 8-16, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Page 1-7, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 18-20, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 21-26, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 28-35, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Page 35, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 38-41, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Pages 42-43, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Page 45: (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Ten: Page 45: (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 3-6, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 7-11, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 15-16, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 18-19, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 25-33, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 35-42, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 43-45, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 46-51, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 52-61, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 61-62, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 63-65, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 65-68, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 69-71, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Page 72, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Page 73, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Page 74-79, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 80-82, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Page 85, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 87-98, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 99-101, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 103-105, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 106-112, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 113-118, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 119-126, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 127-129, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 130-135, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 141-146, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 148-151, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 152-155, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 156-157, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 157-158, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook Eleven: Pages 159-160, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook Nineteen: Loose Materials: Proclamation: Constitution Week, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook Twenty: Loose Materials: Yearbook: Henry Downs Chapter, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-One: Loose Materials: Program: Veterans Affairs Voluntary Service Ceremony, 2001 July 7 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Two: Loose Materials: Printed Materials, 2002, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Three: Loose Materials: Press Book, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Three: Loose Materials: Proclamation: Constitution Week, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Scrapbook: Unidentified: Loose Materials, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook One, 1901-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Eight, 1978-1980 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Twelve, 1986-1988 (Box 33 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Thirteen, 1988-1990 (Box 33 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Fourteen, 1990-1992 (Box 34 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Fifteen, 1992-1994 (Box 34 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Sixteen, 1994-1996 (Box 35 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Seventeen, 1995-1996 (Box 35 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Eighteen, 1996-1998 (Box 36 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Nineteen, 1997-1999 (Box 36 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Twenty, 1999-2000 (Box 37 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-One, 2001-2002 (Box 37 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Two, 2002-2003 (Box 38 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Three, 2004-2005 (Box 38 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Twenty-Four, 1984-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)